Urban Borderlands Records MS083
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Fall 2006, MS083.005; 1.2 Linear Feet; 27 Digital Object(s)
  - The Brazilian Immigrant Experience: A study on the evolution of a Brazilian community in Somverville and the Greater Boston Area [Transcription], 2006; MS083.005.024.00008; Becker, Daniel (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Centre Presente: Building communities and awareness of rights among the Latin American Immigrant population in Massachusetts [Final Report], 2006; MS083.005.024.00009; Grossman-Crist, Shoshana (Box MS083 Shared 1)
    Final project report by Shoshana Grossman-Crist.
  - Centre Presente: Building communities and awareness of rights among the Latin American Immigrant population in Massachusetts [CD files], 2006; MS083.005.024.00010; Grossman-Crist, Shoshana
  - Centre Presente: Building communities and awareness of rights among the Latin American Immigrant population in Massachusetts [Administrative Data], 2006; MS083.005.024.00011; Grossman-Crist, Shoshana (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Centre Presente: Building communities and awareness of rights among the Latin American Immigrant population in Massachusetts [Release Forms], 2006; MS083.005.024.00012; Grossman-Crist, Shoshana (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Centre Presente: Building communities and awareness of rights among the Latin American Immigrant population in Massachusetts [Interview Reports], 2006; MS083.005.024.00013; Grossman-Crist, Shoshana (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Centre Presente: Building communities and awareness of rights among the Latin American Immigrant population in Massachusetts [Transcription], 2006; MS083.005.024.00014; Grossman-Crist, Shoshana (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Women's Stories: The Latina experience in Somerville [Final Report], 2006; MS083.005.024.00015; Hayes, Rebecca (Box MS083 Shared 1)
    Final project report by Rebecca Hayes.
  - Women's Stories: The Latina experience in Somerville [CD files], 2006; MS083.005.024.00016; Hayes, Rebecca
  - Women's Stories: The Latina experience in Somerville [Photo CD files], 2006; MS083.005.024.00017; Hayes, Rebecca
  - Women's Stories: The Latina experience in Somerville [Administrative Data], 2006; MS083.005.024.00018; Hayes, Rebecca (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Women's Stories: The Latina experience in Somerville [Release Forms], 2006; MS083.005.024.00019; Hayes, Rebecca (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Women's Stories: The Latina experience in Somerville [Interview Reports], 2006; MS083.005.024.00020; Hayes, Rebecca (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Women's Stories: The Latina experience in Somerville [Transcription], 2006; MS083.005.024.00021; Hayes, Rebecca (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Change and challenge in the education system: Latino students in Somerville [Final Report], 2006; MS083.005.024.00022; Norsworthy, Marcelo (Box MS083 Shared 1)
    Final project report by Marcelo Norsworthy.
  - Change and challenge in the education system: Latino students in Somerville [CD file], 2006; MS083.005.024.00023; Hayes, Rebecca
  - Change and challenge in the education system: Latino students in Somerville [CD files], 2006; MS083.005.024.00024; Norsworthy, Marcelo
  - Change and challenge in the education system: Latino students in Somerville [Release Forms], 2006; MS083.005.024.00025; Norsworthy, Marcelo (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Change and challenge in the education system: Latino students in Somerville [Interview Reports], 2006; MS083.005.024.00026; Norsworthy, Marcelo (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Change and challenge in the education system: Latino students in Somerville [Draft], 2006; MS083.005.024.00027; Norsworthy, Marcelo (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Joga com Alegria, Joga Futebol: A journey to the heart of Brazilian soccer in Somerville and the Greater Boston Area [Final Report], 2006; MS083.005.024.00028; Rajbhandari, Amod (Box MS083 Shared 1)
    Final project report by Amod Rajbhandari.
  - Joga com Alegria, Joga Futebol: A journey to the heart of Brazilian soccer in Somerville and the Greater Boston Area [CD files], 2006; MS083.005.024.00029; Rajbhandari, Amod
  - Joga com Alegria, Joga Futebol: A journey to the heart of Brazilian soccer in Somerville and the Greater Boston Area [Administrative Data], 2006; MS083.005.024.00030; Rajbhandari, Amod (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Joga com Alegria, Joga Futebol: A journey to the heart of Brazilian soccer in Somerville and the Greater Boston Area [Interview Reports], 2006; MS083.005.024.00031; Rajbhandari, Amod (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Joga com Alegria, Joga Futebol: A journey to the heart of Brazilian soccer in Somerville and the Greater Boston Area [Transcript], 2006; MS083.005.024.00032; Rajbhandari, Amod (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Latino Leadership: Civic and political participation of Latinos in Somerville [Final Report], 2006; MS083.005.024.00033; Villalobos Zamora, Diego (Box MS083 Shared 1)
    Final project report by Diego Villalobos Zamora.
  - Latino Leadership: Civic and political participation of Latinos in Somerville [CD], 2006; MS083.005.024.00034; Villalobos Zamora, Diego (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Latino Leadership: Civic and political participation of Latinos in Somerville [Release Forms], 2006; MS083.005.024.00035; Villalobos Zamora, Diego (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Latino Leadership: Civic and political participation of Latinos in Somerville [Interview Reports], 2006; MS083.005.024.00036; Villalobos Zamora, Diego (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Latino Leadership: Civic and political participation of Latinos in Somerville [Transcription], 2006; MS083.005.024.00037; Villalobos Zamora, Diego (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - The Brazilian Immigrant Experience, interviews with Terry, Jennifer Burtner, 2006-09-18 -- 2006-09-26; MS083.005.025.00001; Becker, Daniel (Case MS083 Shared 2)
    Interviewed by Daniel Brasil Becker for "The Brazilian Immigrant Experience: A study on the evolution of a Brazilian community in Somverville and the Greater Boston Area". Terry recorded September 18, 2006. Jennifer Burtner recorded September 26, 2006.
    audiocassette
  - The Brazilian Immigrant Experience, interviews with Fausto Mendes da Rocha, Pastor Carlos M. Ferreira, 2006-10-02 -- 2006-10-07; MS083.005.025.00002; Becker, Daniel (Case MS083 Shared 2)
    Interviewed by Daniel Brasil Becker for "The Brazilian Immigrant Experience: A study on the evolution of a Brazilian community in Somverville and the Greater Boston Area". Fausto Mendes da Rocha, 2006-10-02; Pastor Carlos M. Ferreira, 2006-10-07.
  - The Brazilian Immigrant Experience, interview with Regina Bertholdo, 2006-10-12; MS083.005.025.00003; Becker, Daniel (Case MS083 Shared 2)
    Interviewed by Daniel Brasil Becker for "The Brazilian Immigrant Experience: A study on the evolution of a Brazilian community in Somverville and the Greater Boston Area"
  - The Brazilian Immigrant Experience, interviews with Edirson Paiva, Fabio, 2006-10-19 -- 2006-12-02; MS083.005.025.00004; Becker, Daniel (Case MS083 Shared 2)
    Interviewed by Daniel Brasil Becker for "The Brazilian Immigrant Experience: A study on the evolution of a Brazilian community in Somverville and the Greater Boston Area". Edirson Paiva, 2006-10-19; Fabio, 2006-12-02.
  - The Brazilian Immigrant Experience, interview with Valter Vitorino, 2006-11-27; MS083.005.025.00005; Becker, Daniel (Case MS083 Shared 2)
  - The Brazilian Immigrant Experience, interviews with Eduardo, Ophelio Steadman, 2006-11-27 -- 2006-11-30; MS083.005.025.00006; Becker, Daniel (Case MS083 Shared 2)
    Interviewed by Daniel Brasil Becker for "The Brazilian Immigrant Experience: A study on the evolution of a Brazilian community in Somverville and the Greater Boston Area". Eduardo, 2006-11-27; Ophelio Steadman, 2006-11-30.
  - The Brazilian Immigrant Experience, interview with Naiara Souto, 2006-12-12; MS083.005.025.00007; Becker, Daniel (Case MS083 Shared 2)
  - Centre Presente, interview with Zuleika Andrade, 2006-09-18; MS083.005.025.00008; Grossman-Crist, Shoshana (Case MS083 Shared 2)
    Interviewed by Shoshana Grossman-Crist for "Centre Presente: Building communities and awareness of rights among the Latin American Immigrant population in Massachusetts"
  - Centre Presente, interview with Elsy Chevez, 2006-09-25; MS083.005.025.00009; Grossman-Crist, Shoshana (Case MS083 Shared 2)
  - Centre Presente, interview with Rafael (pseudonym), 2006-10-30; MS083.005.025.00010; Grossman-Crist, Shoshana (Case MS083 Shared 2)
  - Centre Presente, interview with Maria de la Luz Fuster Huerta, 2006-11-04; MS083.005.025.00011; Grossman-Crist, Shoshana (Case MS083 Shared 2)
  - Centre Presente, interview with Rosa Geurra, 2006-11-04; MS083.005.025.00012; Grossman-Crist, Shoshana (Case MS083 Shared 2)
  - Centre Presente, interviews with Victor Leiva and Wilson Perez, 2006-11-16; MS083.005.025.00013; Grossman-Crist, Shoshana (Case MS083 Shared 2)
  - Centre Presente, interview with Zuleika Andrade, 2006-11-20; MS083.005.025.00014; Grossman-Crist, Shoshana (Case MS083 Shared 2)
  - Women's Stories, interviews with Beatrice Senor, Zuleika Andrade and Nadia Pineda, 2006-09 -- 2006-10; MS083.005.025.00015; Hayes, Rebecca (Case MS083 Shared 2)
    Interviewed by Rebecca Hayes for "Women's Stories: The Latina experience in Somerville"
  - Women's Stories, interview with Mayra Valladares, 2006-10-27; MS083.005.025.00016; Hayes, Rebecca (Case MS083 Shared 2)
  - Women's Stories, interview with Rosa Maria Aguilar, 2006-10-28; MS083.005.025.00017; Hayes, Rebecca (Case MS083 Shared 2)
  - Women's Stories, interview with Consuelo Perez, 2006-11-06; MS083.005.025.00018; Hayes, Rebecca (Case MS083 Shared 2)
  - Women's Stories, interview with Elsie Lopez, 2006-12-17; MS083.005.025.00019; Hayes, Rebecca (Case MS083 Shared 2)
  - Change and challenge in the education system, interviews with Sarah Davila, Aru Manrique, Steve Cohen, 2006-09-26 -- 2006-10-03; MS083.005.025.00020; Norsworthy, Marcelo (Case MS083 Shared 2)
    Interviewed by Marcelo Norsworthy for "Change and challenge in the education system: Latino students in Somerville". Sarah Davila, 2006-09-26; Aru Manrique, 2006-09-28; Steve Cohen, 2006-10-03.
  - Change and challenge in the education system, interview with Patricia Davenport, 2006-10-19; MS083.005.025.00021; Norsworthy, Marcelo (Case MS083 Shared 2)
    Interviewed by Marcelo Norsworthy for "Change and challenge in the education system: Latino students in Somerville"
  - Change and challenge in the education system, interviews with Marjorie Kirsein; Sidia Escobar; Cira Espinosa, 2006; MS083.005.025.00022; Norsworthy, Marcelo (Case MS083 Shared 2)
  - Joga com Alegria, Joga Futebol, interview with Marcos Garcia, 2006; MS083.005.025.00023; Rajbhandari, Amod
  - Joga com Alegria, Joga Futebol, interview with Arlon Acua Renga, 2006; MS083.005.025.00024; Rajbhandari, Amod
  - Joga com Alegria, Joga Futebol, interview with Aruman Reque, 2006; MS083.005.025.00025; Rajbhandari, Amod
  - Joga com Alegria, Joga Futebol, interview with Daniel Brasil Becker, 2006; MS083.005.025.00026; Rajbhandari, Amod
  - Joga com Alegria, Joga Futebol, interview with Fabio Gomez, 2006; MS083.005.025.00027; Rajbhandari, Amod
  - Joga com Alegria, Joga Futebol, interview with Daniel Brasil Becker, 2006; MS083.005.025.00028; Rajbhandari, Amod
  - Joga com Alegria, Joga Futebol, interviews, 2006; MS083.005.025.00029; Rajbhandari, Amod
    - Joga com Alegria, Joga Futebol, interview with Marvi Hernandez, 2006; MS083.005.025.00029.00001; Rajbhandari, Amod
    - Joga com Alegria, Joga Futebol, interview with Wilson, 2006; MS083.005.025.00029.00002; Rajbhandari, Amod
    - Joga com Alegria, Joga Futebol, interview with Fernando Silva, 2006; MS083.005.025.00029.00003; Rajbhandari, Amod
  - Joga com Alegria, Joga Futebol, interview with Cristiano Fernandez, 2006; MS083.005.025.00030; Rajbhandari, Amod
  - Joga com Alegria, Joga Futebol, interview with Daniel Brasil Becker, 2006; MS083.005.025.00031; Rajbhandari, Amod
  - Joga com Alegria, Joga Futebol, interview with Fernando Silva, 2006; MS083.005.025.00032; Rajbhandari, Amod
- Fall 2008, 1990 -- 2008; MS083.006; 1.2 Linear Feet; 27 Digital Object(s)
  This series consists of materials from the Fall 2008 semester.
  This series is arranged by creator and material type.
  - Press reports - Latinos in Somerville [Binder, 1 of 2], 1990 -- 2004; MS083.006.024.00038 (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Press reports - Latinos in Somerville [Binder, 2 of 2], 1990 -- 2004; MS083.006.024.00039 (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Making Music to Make a Home: The Roles of Brazilizian Music in Somerville [Administrative materials], 2008; MS083.006.024.00040; Burg, Abigail (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Making Music to Make a Home: The Roles of Brazilizian Music in Somerville [Interview Reports], 2008; MS083.006.024.00041; Burg, Abigail (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Making Music to Make a Home: The Roles of Brazilizian Music in Somerville [Transcript], 2008; MS083.006.024.00042; Burg, Abigail (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Making Music to Make a Home: The Roles of Brazilizian Music in Somerville [Report], 2008; MS083.006.024.00043; Burg, Abigail (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Making Music to Make a Home: The Roles of Brazilizian Music in Somerville [CD data], 2008; MS083.006.024.00044; Burg, Abigail
  - Reinventing Tradition: The music and dance of Latin American in Somerville, MA [Administrative materials], 2008; MS083.006.024.00045; Driscoll, Sarah (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Reinventing Tradition: The music and dance of Latin American in Somerville, MA [Interview reports], 2008; MS083.006.024.00046; Driscoll, Sarah (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Reinventing Tradition: The music and dance of Latin American in Somerville, MA [Transcript], 2008; MS083.006.024.00047; Driscoll, Sarah (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Reinventing Tradition: The music and dance of Latin American in Somerville, MA [Report], 2008; MS083.006.024.00048; Driscoll, Sarah (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Reinventing Tradition: The music and dance of Latin American in Somerville, MA [CD data], 2008; MS083.006.024.00049; Driscoll, Sarah
  - Sounding out Identity: The Place of Female Brazilian Singers in Greater Somerville [Administrative Data], 2008; MS083.006.024.00050; Felsman, Caitlin (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Sounding out Identity: The Place of Female Brazilian Singers in Greater Somerville [Interview Reports], 2008; MS083.006.024.00051; Felsman, Caitlin (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Sounding out Identity: The Place of Female Brazilian Singers in Greater Somerville [Transcript], 2008; MS083.006.024.00052; Felsman, Caitlin (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Sounding out Identity: The Place of Female Brazilian Singers in Greater Somerville [Report], 2008; MS083.006.024.00053; Felsman, Caitlin (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Sounding out Identity: The Place of Female Brazilian Singers in Greater Somerville [CD Data], 2008; MS083.006.024.00054; Felsman, Caitlin
  - Bridges and Barriers: Latino Visual Artistic Expression in Somerville, MA [Administrative Materials], 2008; MS083.006.024.00055; Mitarotondo, Julia (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Bridges and Barriers: Latino Visual Artistic Expression in Somerville, MA [Interview Reports], 2008; MS083.006.024.00056; Mitarotondo, Julia (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Bridges and Barriers: Latino Visual Artistic Expression in Somerville, MA [Transcript], 2008; MS083.006.024.00057; Mitarotondo, Julia (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Bridges and Barriers: Latino Visual Artistic Expression in Somerville, MA [Report], 2008; MS083.006.024.00058; Mitarotondo, Julia (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Bridges and Barriers: Latino Visual Artistic Expression in Somerville, MA [CD Data], 2008; MS083.006.024.00059; Mitarotondo, Julia
  - 'Joga de Capoeira': The Dance Fight Game from Brazil to Somerville [Administrative Data], 2008; MS083.006.024.00060; Lebron-Torres, Namibia (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - 'Joga de Capoeira': The Dance Fight Game from Brazil to Somerville [Interview Reports], 2008; MS083.006.024.00061; Lebron-Torres, Namibia (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - 'Joga de Capoeira': The Dance Fight Game from Brazil to Somerville [Transcript], 2008; MS083.006.024.00062; Lebron-Torres, Namibia (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - 'Joga de Capoeira': The Dance Fight Game from Brazil to Somerville [Report], 2008; MS083.006.024.00063; Lebron-Torres, Namibia (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - 'Joga de Capoeira': The Dance Fight Game from Brazil to Somerville [Data CD], 2008; MS083.006.024.00064; Lebron-Torres, Namibia
  - 'Joga de Capoeira': The Dance Fight Game from Brazil to Somerville [Data CD], 2008; MS083.006.024.00065; Lebron-Torres, Namibia
    Contains pictures
  - Bringing Latino Culture to the Streets: Community Development through Art in East Somerville [Administrative Data], 2008; MS083.006.024.00066; Pierson, Anna (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Bringing Latino Culture to the Streets: Community Development through Art in East Somerville [Interview Reports], 2008; MS083.006.024.00067; Pierson, Anna (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Bringing Latino Culture to the Streets: Community Development through Art in East Somerville [Transcript], 2008; MS083.006.024.00068; Pierson, Anna (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Bringing Latino Culture to the Streets: Community Development through Art in East Somerville [Report], 2008; MS083.006.024.00069; Pierson, Anna (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Bringing Latino Culture to the Streets: Community Development through Art in East Somerville [Data CD], 2008; MS083.006.024.00070; Pierson, Anna
  - Latin Dance and Culture in Somerville [Administrative Data], 2008; MS083.006.024.00071; Schiff, Julia (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Latin Dance and Culture in Somerville [Interview Reports], 2008; MS083.006.024.00072; Schiff, Julia (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Latin Dance and Culture in Somerville [Transcript], 2008; MS083.006.024.00073; Schiff, Julia (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Latin Dance and Culture in Somerville [Report], 2008; MS083.006.024.00074; Schiff, Julia (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Latin Dance and Culture in Somerville [Data CD], 2008; MS083.006.024.00075; Schiff, Julia
  - Painting, Singing and Dancing Ourselves: The Role of Artistic Production in Young Latinos' Development in Somerville, MA [Administrative Data], 2008; MS083.006.024.00076; Slocum, Juliana (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Painting, Singing and Dancing Ourselves: The Role of Artistic Production in Young Latinos' Development in Somerville, MA [Interview Reports], 2008; MS083.006.024.00077; Slocum, Juliana (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Painting, Singing and Dancing Ourselves: The Role of Artistic Production in Young Latinos' Development in Somerville, MA [Transcript], 2008; MS083.006.024.00078; Slocum, Juliana (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Painting, Singing and Dancing Ourselves: The Role of Artistic Production in Young Latinos' Development in Somerville, MA [Report], 2008; MS083.006.024.00079; Slocum, Juliana (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Painting, Singing and Dancing Ourselves: The Role of Artistic Production in Young Latinos' Development in Somerville, MA [Data CD], 2008; MS083.006.024.00080; Slocum, Juliana
  - 'This is my Language' Agency, Identity and Community among Latino/a Artists in Somerville [Administrative Data], 2008; MS083.006.024.00081; Sofio, Jessica (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - 'This is my Language' Agency, Identity and Community among Latino/a Artists in Somerville [Interview Reports], 2008; MS083.006.024.00082; Sofio, Jessica (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - 'This is my Language' Agency, Identity and Community among Latino/a Artists in Somerville [Transcript], 2008; MS083.006.024.00083; Sofio, Jessica (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - 'This is my Language' Agency, Identity and Community among Latino/a Artists in Somerville [Report], 2008; MS083.006.024.00084; Sofio, Jessica (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - 'This is my Language' Agency, Identity and Community among Latino/a Artists in Somerville [Data CD], 2008; MS083.006.024.00085; Sofio, Jessica
  - Making Music to Make a Home - Burg - microcassette 1 - Scoccia and Santos, 2008-10-09 -- 2008-10-10; MS083.006.025.00033; Burg, Abigail (Case MS083 Shared 2)
    Scoccia 10-9-08 and Santos 10-10-08
  - Making Music to Make a Home - Burg - microcassette 2 - Borges and Santos, 2008-10-26 -- 2008-11-14; MS083.006.025.00034; Burg, Abigail (Case MS083 Shared 2)
    Borges 10-26-08 and Santos 11-14-08
  - Making Music to Make a Home - Burg - microcassette 3 - Gondim and First Night Performance with Santos, 2008-11-01 -- 2008-11-14; MS083.006.025.00035; Burg, Abigail (Case MS083 Shared 2)
    Gondim 11-01-08 and First Night Performance with Santos 11-14-08
  - Reinventing Tradition: The music and dance of Latin America in Somerville, MA - Interview with Daniella Malta and Gina Cachimuel, 2008-10-29 -- 2008-11-01; MS083.006.025.00036; Driscoll, Sarah (Case MS083 Shared 2)
    Daniella Malta 11-1-08 and Gina Cachimuel 10-29-08
  - Reinventing Tradition: The music and dance of Latin America in Somerville, MA - Interview with Luciana Araripe, 2008-11-13; MS083.006.025.00037; Driscoll, Sarah (Case MS083 Shared 2)
  - Reinventing Tradition: The music and dance of Latin America in Somerville, MA - Interview with Rosangela Santiagoand Santos Alva, 2008-10-10 -- 2008-10-19; MS083.006.025.00038; Driscoll, Sarah (Case MS083 Shared 2)
    Rosangela Santiago 10-10-08 and Santos Alva 10-19-08
  - Bridges and Barriers: Latino Visual Artistic Expression in Somerville, MA - Wil Renderos, Carrie Dancy, and Bernal Murillo, 2008-10-15 -- 2008-10-22; MS083.006.025.00039; Mitarotondo, Julia (Case MS083 Shared 2)
    Wil Renderos 10-17-08, Carrie Dancy 10-22-08, and Bernal Murillo 10-15-08
  - Bridges and Barriers: Latino Visual Artistic Expression in Somerville, MA - Greg Jenkins phone interview, Raul Gonzalez, Alexandre Emmanuel, 2008-11-08 -- 2008-11-09; MS083.006.025.00040; Mitarotondo, Julia (Case MS083 Shared 2)
    Raul Gonzalez 11-08-08, Alexandre Emmanuel 11-09-08
  - Sounding out Identity: The Place of Female Brazilian Singers in Greater Somerville [Interview Audio], 2008; MS083.006.025.00041; Felsman, Caitlin
  - 'Joga de Capoeira', interview with Jason Ri, 2008; MS083.006.025.00042; Lebron-Torres, Namibia
  - 'Joga de Capoeira', interviews with instructor Caveira, 2008; MS083.006.025.00043; Lebron-Torres, Namibia
  - 'Joga de Capoeira', interviews with Mestre Deraldo Ferreira, 2008; MS083.006.025.00044; Lebron-Torres, Namibia
  - 'Joga de Capoeira', interviews with Luana Silva, 2008; MS083.006.025.00045; Lebron-Torres, Namibia
  - 'Joga de Capoeira', interview with Roberto Carlo Ruiz Morales, 2008; MS083.006.025.00046; Lebron-Torres, Namibia
  - 'Joga de Capoeira', interview with Wendy Kinol, 2008; MS083.006.025.00047; Lebron-Torres, Namibia
  - 'Joga de Capoeira', interviews with Eileen Guo, 2008; MS083.006.025.00048; Lebron-Torres, Namibia
  - Bringing Latino Culture to the Streets - Pierson/Dancy, 2008-10-15; MS083.006.025.00049; Pierson, Anna (Case MS083 Shared 2)
    Anna Pierson Urban Borderlands #1; Side A Pierson/Dancy 10/15/08 and Side B Pierson/Dancy 10/15/08.
    audio tape
  - Bringing Latino Culture to the Streets - Pierson/Marques, Pierson/Emmanuel, Pierson/Oliveira, Pierson/Poteet, 2008-10-21 -- 2008-12-13; MS083.006.025.00050; Pierson, Anna (Case MS083 Shared 2)
    Anna Pierson Urban Borderlands #2; Side A Pierson/Marques 10/21/08, Pierson/Emmanuel 10/28/08, Pierson/Oliveira 11/1/08 Part 1 and Side B Pierson/Oliveria 11/1/08 part 2 and Pierson/Poteet 12/13/08.
  - Latin Dance in Somerville - J. Schiff Urban Borderlands 08 Disk 1/2, 2008-10-10 -- 2008-10-26; MS083.006.025.00051; Schiff, Julia (Case MS083 Shared 2)
    J. Schiff Latin Dance in Somerville Urban Borderland 08 Disk 1/2 Side A: Interviews with Michell Rubiera Oct 10 08 and Andres Giraldo Oct 17 08 and Side B: Itamar Sangiorgio Oct 26 08.
  - Latin Dance in Somerville - J. Schiff Urban Borderlands 08 Disk 2/2, 2008-10-29 -- 2008-12-08; MS083.006.025.00052; Schiff, Julia (Case MS083 Shared 2)